<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">视频天下</string>


    <string name="nav_homepage">首页</string>
    <string name="nav_featured_site">精选专区</string>
    <string name="nav_channel_category">频道分类</string>
    <string name="nav_my_video">我的视频</string>
    <string name="nav_search">一键搜索</string>
    <string name="nav_setting">系统设置</string>

    <string name="nav_tab_image">主导航条图标</string>


    <string name="topic_by_hot">按热门</string>
    <string name="topic_by_time">按更新</string>
    <string name="topic_filter">筛选</string>

    <string name="detail_play">播放</string>
    <string name="content_description_image">image</string>
    <string name="content_description_shadow">shadow</string>


    <string name="sample_text">咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔咔</string>
</resources>